Last time on Zombieland Saga, I and Junko got into a huge fight right before Saga Rock.
They were like, grr, grr, and my brain was like, yikes, how am I supposed to fix this problem?
But then on the day of the festival, Junko was like, rawr, I'm awesome again, and my heart was like, oh, yay!
And even though the thunder was like, boom, boom, we had a huge crowd that was like, woo, woo!
Then some bad stuff happened and we were like, uh-oh, but then we all worked together, like, let's do this!
Now the legend of Fransha Shou can be like, go, go! Or at least, I hope so.
Oh! Saki, look! Here we are!
Saga Rock was so great! I'm glad we all got to go!
That's the reporter who wrote about our trip to the hot spring.
We're getting buzzed. There have been lots of posts in the past month.
I think we're about to see a ton of responses, positive and negative.
So cool! I think I dazzled people the most!
Really? I don't see you.
Oh, right there!
Sorry you're so tiny.
I didn't ask you, Saki.
Well, I think you were totally dazzling.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
You have the kind of smile that lights a baroon.
And that star is so cute.
Thank you!
Hamamoto, what's your lunch order?
Sicilian rice bowl.
Yep, should have guessed.
How about you?
Nothing for me.
Okay.
Be back soon.
Sure.
Does Scully for lunch every day or what?
It's because he hates TV.
Ah, seems like a lot of people have moved past it, huh?
That's not exactly why, but yeah.
It's because he's a salad too.
Great service with a smart...
Sweetheart, what are you doing?
Come along now.
Oh.
Ah.
Good morning!
Good morning, sir.
It's nice to see you.
Well, ladies, congrats on the great press.
So, Zuko, what were your thoughts about the Saga Rock Festival?
Oh, um, it shows we have potential, you know?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You're writing on a wave of popularity.
She seems better.
And how about you?
Are you enjoying the ride?
Me? I don't know.
I, uh, are you going to say don't get cocky?
Do get cocky!
You're in a magazine, aren't you?
Stick out your Pinocchio nose if you're going to ride this hype wave.
Surf, bro.
How do you like it, Lily?
Is that star thingy on your skull getting bigger?
No, that's dope!
Oh, what's the matter, kiddo?
What did I do?
Hurt your fee-fees?
Is your star going to get all big like the rocks at Kewski Park?
That'd be cool, right?
Jeez, you're so damn creepy!
Anyway, if we want a real fan uprising, we'll need to use every advantage we can rustle up.
Soon will be a household name that every man, woman, and child in Saga knows.
Pop-up shows, meetups, TV spots.
If there's an eyeball open, I want you in it.
Let's have a good old-fashioned zombie outbreak!
Who's ready for a photo op with your favorite idol, huh?
By the way, you can also get a signed glamour shot from number four!
And please remember that touching is prohibited.
Don't be creepy.
Don't look now, but we've got trouble.
What happened?
Whoa, he's giant!
Yeah, that guy's Yakuza, no doubt about it.
You think?
Maybe Shade's got in some trouble and he's here to collect.
That sounds bad.
Wait, where's Mr. Kotaro?
He must have run for the hills.
Looks like he wants to get a photo, huh?
He's here for the runt?
Guess he's a fan of lilies.
I wouldn't let my guard down just yet.
If we're big enough to be in Saga-Zine, then there's gonna be a few weirdos.
For all we know, he came here to kidnap the little squirt.
Oh, God!
Your show is so amazing!
I'll come again!
Thanks a lot!
Bye-bye!
Nice to meet you!
I'm number six!
You...
You really...
Hell no!
I don't think so, buddy!
Let's step back, okay?
But...
Wait!
That was my...
I'm rolling so much!
She gave me a fright.
I nearly wet me knickers.
Yeah, that number two girl's hardcore!
That guy's lucky!
Hmm?
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh, yeah!
Oh, oh!
Excuse me?
Um, there's trouble!
We told you no touching the talent!
Got that?
I'm sorry.
It's just...
That girl looks like...
Spit it out, would ya?
Seven years ago, there was this famous child TV actor by the name of Lily Hoshikawa.
What happened to Lily could happen to any of us, especially to Junko and me.
You're right.
We don't use names, but people know our faces.
I'm afraid that being a public figure is quite dangerous.
More so now than ever.
This is such a friggin' drag.
Hang on.
Don't you think Lily should be done washing up by now?
I didn't see you next to the faucet, so I got worried.
Wanna talk?
Look, Sakura.
That guy from before.
Well, see, he was actually my papa.
Huh?
Your dad's...
Yakuza?
He's what?
No way!
He was enormous!
Well, I take after my mama.
I didn't think he would ever show up at one of our fan events.
Must be weird.
Honestly?
I've been trying my hardest to forget about him.
But now I can't.
It was usually just the two of us.
But still, I was never lonely.
I knew that Mama was watching over us from up in the sky.
And we had a TV set, too.
Papa's favorite thing to do was relax in front of the TV together.
He used to say, no matter how good a show was,
it was even better if you could laugh and cry along with another person while you watch.
He'd always want me to sit next to him on the couch.
Even if I had homework.
Seeing how much he enjoyed TV made me really happy.
So I thought it'd be nice if I could make him smile from inside the TV.
I signed with a children's talent agency,
and then he quit his job so he could be my manager.
Whenever I had work, Papa was right there with me.
And of course, I was adorable and talented from the get-go,
so every show I was a part of turned into a big hit automatically.
But as soon as I made it to the top, something real bad happened to me.
Open the door, Masao.
They can't get the show moving without you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't worry.
They can edit that part out.
All that matters to you is the me that's on the screen.
You don't care about the real me.
You know that's not true.
It's just some leg hair.
It means you're growing up, that's all.
No, I'm never growing up!
You can't look that way forever, you know.
Yes, I can, and I'm going to.
I don't want to look like you, Papa!
Leave me alone!
Masao, this is your job.
Lots of people are excited for this show.
Now come out!
I'll always be just like this.
Do I have some food stuck on my face?
That's enough!
I'm coming in!
Please wake up!
Masao!
That was the last time I saw Papa.
Um, wait.
So what happened?
Sorry, it was kind of hard to keep up.
Who's this Masao guy you were talking about?
It's what my name used to be.
Uh, oh!
What?!
There you have it.
Lily used to be Masao.
I mostly can't believe you dropped dead over a dumb whisker.
How lame is that?
Saki, quit!
Wait, so you had a totally different name, right?
Yeah, Masao-go.
That's so crazy all this time and we still had no idea!
Tell us your dad's name too!
It's Takeo-go.
They're such manly names!
Stop being a jerk!
I'm not laughing at you!
It's just too perfect!
Wow, this is unexpected.
Masao-go.
Okay, so what happens now?
I'm still the same Lily and always will be.
And now I won't ever grow up.
There's no need to worry.
I guess not.
Wait, so did he know this?
Of course I knew about her.
I am so gonna kill you!
What?!
So you've got room for Lily in your little girly club,
but Masao's not welcome?!
I said I'm not Masao, I'm Lily!
Right, she's not Masao, she's Lily!
You guys are Masao, I'm Lily!
Anyway, you've got a big show tomorrow!
If you have time for tired-ass questions,
you might as well go to bed, you brain-dead brats!
Aw, she's so cute.
We've been working so close together and we never realized.
Who cares?
Why does it matter what kind of equipment she's got?
Equipment?
We're all dead, we've still got that in common.
You know, it begs the question of what zombies are,
to think that we'll never age.
It's not all bad.
Lily gets to stay young,
and none of us will ever change either.
It's kinda nice.
Look at this!
We got excellent ratings!
That means you've impressed a lot of people with your acting!
Today's special guest is Miss Lily Hoshikawa.
Thanks for having me!
You see that?
Woo!
You're a natural!
Keep it up!
Papa?
They miss that adorable look you gave there!
Hey, I was wondering if the two of us could go somewhere together.
Where is that, dear?
I want to go back to Kono Park.
Just you and me.
Sure.
Yeah, as soon as filming for this show is finished.
Yep, he's the best!
We think it was caused by a mental shock.
To die from that,
the brain must have been under great distress before the fall.
Papa!
It's a bad death!
Get a grip.
That girl's not Musou.
She couldn't be.
Hi again.
Sorry about last time.
Number two didn't mean you any harm.
No, it was totally my fault.
So, uh, could I get a t-shirt?
Uh-huh.
I don't think it'll fit you, though.
You wear a 5X.
How'd you know that?
Well, we meet a lot of fans, so it's easy to guess.
I see.
In that case, an extra small.
You see, I used to have a kid about your age.
But, uh, I wasn't what you'd call the best dad.
I was so focused on myself, I couldn't care for my child properly.
I hope that your father's a nice man.
Uh-huh.
Pa, I mean, my father's really great.
He's the sweetest and kindest ever.
Thanks a lot.
And I'm sorry for frightening you before.
I won't bother you again.
I'm just here to apologize.
Goodbye.
You okay?
Yeah, totally.
Why wouldn't I be?
I guess we should get back to practice, huh?
It's cool.
We were thinking you might need a little more time to yourself.
You know what?
I bet you I'd be better off if I was like you and didn't have any memories.
No way.
It's great you and your dad met again.
I mean, if you didn't remember each other, then you wouldn't understand your feelings.
Papa, I've been gone so long, but he still loves me.
And I...
I still...
That kind of makes me think people must be busted up over us, too.
I can't figure out what this familiar feeling is.
I can kind of remember a single memory.
But where and when was it?
You all right?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Look, we gotta do something and quick!
What can we do?
I'm a zombie now.
Don't give up yet.
We just have to put our heads together.
We'll find a way.
Thanks, Sakura.
I think the answer's clear.
Yeah, and it happens to be something that only Franshushu can do.
But first, we need to ask Kotaro.
Ah, almost forgot.
That came in the mail.
I'll just throw it out.
Man, must be next to impossible for local idols to get popular these days.
Pew!
The show's almost over.
Think he'll be here?
We've done all that we can.
Papa!
Hey!
Guess what?
We got a new song!
And the squirt's gonna be the lead singer!
Saki, you can't call her that.
Uh, right!
I mean number six!
Here's our new song, called To My Dearest.
I knew one day we'd be saying goodbye.
Just never thought it would be so soon.
Never got the chance to tell you everything that I wanted to.
Don't you know?
Every moment I had with you filled my heart with the deepest of emotions.
Through all my tears, and all my fears, you held me near.
You've been there for me, through all of the good and bad.
You showed me so much warmth, how could I go on without you?
You are irreplaceable, and so remarkable.
Even now, even now, your memory hears me say.
I'm really happy that you came out here to see our show.
I've always had a passion for TV, though.
That's why I'm gonna work hard to be on screen a lot.
And when you see me there, I hope it makes you smile.
I can't tell you how much it means to me to look out there and see you.
I promise I won't forget you, and I love you.
In the present, and the future, in my heart you are always with me.
Whether apart, or together, you still inspire me.
Give me courage, through the sorrow.
Give me hope there will be tomorrow.
Keep me safe, always watch over me, my dear.
Every single day, I miss you, I miss you.
It's hard, but I'll get through.
These feelings won't leave me, and that's okay.
Cause real love, yes real love, never fades away.
It's with you always.
I miss you, I miss you, if one day I find you, and you feel the same, would be a dream come true.
Namamoto, what's your lunch order?
Sicilian rice bowl.
Same freaking thing every day.
Hey, one udon. Chicken.
What? So you're gonna eat here today?
Yeah.
These girls are so hilarious.
Yeah, I cracked up when I saw this.
Saki here. Next time, episode 9. Though my life may have ended once by some twist of faith, I have risen and am song and dancer to be my faith, and carrying the memories of my comrades in my heart as I sally forth shall be my saga!